evuln.com 2018-12-29

# eVuln.com : Privacy Policy

## Principles

We have a few fundamental principles about privacy and the information we collect:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * You retain copyright and any other rights you already hold in Content which you submit, post or display through eVuln.com.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals.

## Introduction

eVuln.com operates web-based services. It is eVuln.com's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. This privacy policy describes the choices available to you regarding our use of the personal information we collect and how you can access and update this information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, contact info@eVuln.com.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, eVuln.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. eVuln.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how eVuln.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, eVuln.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

eVuln.com also uses third party tracking-utility partners who use log files to collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. eVuln.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to eVuln.com's websites choose to interact with eVuln.com in ways that require eVuln.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that eVuln.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up as a user at eVuln.com to provide an email address. We also provide them the opportunity to provide additional information such as name and phone number. Those who engage in transactions with eVuln.com – by purchasing a account plan at eVuln.com, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, eVuln.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with eVuln.com. eVuln.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Opt-Out Policy

eVuln.com offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering services at eVuln.com, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties as outlined in this privacy policy, simply send us a request at support@eVuln.com

## Aggregated Statistics

eVuln.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. eVuln.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, eVuln.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Access to Personally-Identifying Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@eVuln.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

eVuln.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on eVuln.com’s behalf or to provide services available at eVuln.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others including a credit card processing company to bill you for goods services and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using eVuln.com websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

eVuln.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, eVuln.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, or when eVuln.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of eVuln.com, third parties or the public at large.

In the event eVuln.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

If you are a registered user of eVuln.com and have supplied your email address, eVuln.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with eVuln.com and our products. . If you wish to no longer receive our newsletters you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email communications you receive.

We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

eVuln.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (suchas a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@eVuln.com.

## Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@eVuln.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. eVuln.com uses cookies to help eVuln.com identify and track visitors, their usage of eVuln.com website, and their website access preferences. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. eVuln.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using eVuln.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of eVuln.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

The use of cookies by our partners is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners use session ID cookies to to help us track the effectiveness of our websites and generate visitor traffic.

## Clear Gifs

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of eVuln.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

## Testimonials

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personallyidentifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to have your testimonial removed please contact us at support@evuln.com.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, eVuln.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in eVuln.com sole discretion. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. eVuln.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: support@evuln.com
